[{"answer": "Well, I think the fact that we're talking about it on Mitt Romney's big night tells you it was a distraction.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "What went -- what went on out there?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Did you find it embarrassing?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "It's a very close race, and so you have to understand success is in the eye of the beholder.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "How do you rate it?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "No!", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Were you palpitating?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Look, Clint Eastwood is Clint Eastwood, and the crowd loved it.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Were you thinking, What the hell is Dirty Harry doing up there?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Mitt.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Who made the better speech, Mitt or Ann Romney?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely, the whole convention.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Has he resonated with America's women?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "You know Clint Eastwood well.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, listen, I think it depends on which side you're on in all of this.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "What did you -- what did you make of what happened tonight?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "I mean, it's pretty dangerous to do that, isn't it?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "I think he was wonderful tonight.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "How did you think Mitt Romney did tonight?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "OIGT: Well, he's going to go back and do the work that he needs to do.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "What's he going to do now?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, I think the fact that the most commentary following Mitt Romney's speech is about an empty chair says more about Mitt Romney than it does about Barack Obama.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "No, I actually thought it was a little bit sad.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "When you saw Clint Eastwood going off like he did, were you punching the air with delight?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Well, I think we're going to have a great convention next week.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "When you -- when you group (ph) next week and have your own convention, what are the warning signals that you have to really be alert to?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "You know, our stars are the middle class and working families and the people that are powering our campaign and that will carry Barack Obama back to the White House for a second term on their shoulders.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Are you grouping (ph) around Hollywood, finding your own stars to speak, or is that idea gone on the back burner now?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "Well, Barack Obama isn't involved with super-PACs.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Are we going to carry on seeing very, very unpleasant attack ads through his super-PAC, the very same super-PAC ads that Barack Obama vowed not get involved with?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Do you believe Karl Rove is still weaving his magic behind the scenes?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Well, it is as simple as that but is the case of election being for sale.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Isn't it as simple as that?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Well, that's a recipe -- you have David Coke in the New York delegation saying he will give as much as $40 million.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "What about saying we're not going to try to win this by money alone?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "To Penn Jillette.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Even in the \"Wall Street Journal\" Rove's own colleagues are saying isn't this a complete perversion of the electoral process?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "I don't know -- if you don't have, that if you don't allow people to spend money, then incumbents always win.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "So when the Supreme Court gave a green license to all of this, you were quite happy, were you, even though the effects surely, surely is that there will be an ever bigger corruption about the American process?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "In this convention, it was awesome.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Does it get any better for a columnist in the history of journalism than Clint Eastwood going bonkers on the stage?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "Who do you make on it?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "You know, there was nothing to say that it was completely da-da.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "It will be, what the hell was Clint Eastwood's smoking?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "I think also the reason it was so tense-worthy for the Romney campaign is that they are the most button downed control campaign that I have ever seen.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Why are you fringing, Maeve?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "He must have clear the empty chairs then.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "But you have Romney advisers staring open-mouthed like statues wondering, what in the hell is he going to say next?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "I think these things are supposed to be very carefully scripted infomercials with this very, very careful messages to frame Mitt Romney as the avatar, this young, new kind of head -- maybe not hip but certainly fresh face for the Republican Party.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "What would it do to the party's reputation that they unleashed Clint Eastwood tonight and he did what he did?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Ryan, did Mitt Romney do enough tonight, do you think, to satisfy not just the party but the outer world?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Mitt Romney, hit or miss?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I think Penn Jillette is auditioning for the role of Clint Eastwood next week.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Ben?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "I think Obama really needs to lay out his agenda for a second term and we are still waiting for that.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Maeve?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "I want - I think he can get Clint Eastwood to come to both conventions.", "docId": "120830pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Joel?", "qSentId": 633}]